This subtitle is a fan-made translation and
not affiliated with the original content creators.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(fireworks bursting)
(mellow celebratory song playing)
♪ It's the last night of the year ♪
♪ It is time
To gather everyone near ♪
♪ Fireworks have lit up the sky ♪
♪ Dance with me now
And don't you be shy ♪
♪ Forgive and forget
Live and let live ♪
♪ These are some things
We will say ♪
♪ Don't really know
What tomorrow will be ♪
♪ Up until morning we'll stay ♪
Dad. come... dance with us!
♪ It's the last night of the year ♪
Dad. come.
Joe...
take care of Granny.
Remember. after me.
you are the man of the house.
(ominous music)
Bye. Mom.
When will you be back?
I don't know.
(theme song)
(Ana) Pedro. you don't have time.
The murders will take place
at 11:59 p.m.
You have 1.5 hours to find them.
Ana. we're trying.
Madam. your email ID?
ana@anagoretti.com
I'm emailing you
with an IP tracker code.
Email him from your account.
What's an IP tracker?
He opens the email.
and we can track his location.
What should I email him?
(Pedro) Anything...
"Let's meet over a cup of coffee
and discuss it."
If he's a fan. he may respond.
IP tracker sent.
Please don't forget to attach it.
Okay.
(news producer) 9. 8. 7...
6. 5. 4...
3. 2. 1.
Soon. we'll bring in the New Year.
(club music playing)
-If he doesn't open the email?
-No location. Simple.
What's his email ID?
carloslobo1980@mailme.com.
So. his name is Carlos Lobo.
Born in 1980 maybe?
What does the mail say?
"Dear Ana-ji.
"I'll shoot my wife and her lover
at 11:59 p.m. Then. commit suicide."
Sir. I believe he's a gangster
or a cop.
How can you say that?
Who has a gun and bullets?
Cops or gangsters.
Go on.
"I'll leave a letter
at the reception.
"Your breaking news for tomorrow.
"Tell the world I'm not a bad man."
He clearly cares for his reputation.
Correct?
Not a gangster then.
He's definitely a cop.
When you talk about reception...
what comes to mind first?
-Hotel?
-Hotel.
Maybe his wife and her lover
are there?
Possible.
-The murder will happen at a hotel!
-Possible.
Carlos Lobo...
(cheering and laughing)
(glasses clink)
We'll be back after a short break.
(intense music)
(phone ringing)
Yes. Ana?
He opened the email.
What did he say?
He says...
"Sorry. it's too late."
Oh. shit.
Thanks. Ana.
Sir. his location is Canacona.
Where exactly?
I can't see that.
It's an hour to Canacona.
and you only have 50 minutes left.
But where in Canacona?
Sir. let's get out of here.
We'll crack it en route.
Let's go.
-(tyres screech)
-(New Year revellers screech)
Many Carlos' on social media...
Just one from Goa.
Sub inspector.
Age 45.
Know him?
No.
(DJ) 30 minutes to go for 2025!
Everybody. come on...
hands in the air!
Carlos' wife is Rene Lobo.
Jayant. call all hotels in Canacona.
Ask if Rene Lobo has checked in.
Or Nitin Menon. Rene's boyfriend.
Or Nitin Menon. Her boyfriend.
Sure. sir.
Rene Lobo or Nitin Menon.
How did you crack
he's her boyfriend?
It's a no-brainer. sir.
Any idiot can find out.
He "likes" all her posts.
He sends her hearts.
It's obvious.
I mean. it's difficult.
But one can figure it out.
(guests cheering)
(club music continues)
(Jayant) Hotel Santa Catarina
has a guest named Nitin Menon.
Seven minutes.
Pritam. call the hotel.
(phone trilling)
Hello. Hotel Santa Catarina.
How may I assist you?
(Pedro) You have a guest--
-One second. sir.
-His name--
Which room are Rene Lobo
and Nitin Menon in?
-Shit!
Sorry. sir. We cannot give out
our guests' confidential information.
Hello!
He's going to murder them.
Stop him!
Hello?
Hello!
-What an idiot!
-Hello!
Sir. room 706. 7th floor.
Hello? Hello!
Is there an emergency?
They are on Do-Not-Disturb.
Know Ana. the newsreader?
It's for her.
She'll collect it.
Sorry to keep you waiting. sir.
Hello?
(dramatic music)
Where's Carlos?
Sorry. sir. Carlos who?
The guy asking for Rene Lobo's room.
Where is he?
Nitin Menon's room?
Sorry. we can't disclose
that information.
Goa Police.
Where is he?
Sir. room 706. 7th floor.
Carlos just entered the lift.
Tell the lift attendant to push
all the buttons.
Shit!
Sir. the second lift
is out of service.
Sir. staircase!
(phone ringing)
Hello.
(dramatic music continues)
(dramatic music rises)
Shit!
Carlos!
Pedro... Inspector Pedro.
How are you. buddy?
-(gun cocks)
-Why point a gun at me?
I haven't come to fight.
Look. I have a gun too.
-(gunfire)
-(screams)
Come here. Shit!
Count up to ten.
1-2-3-4-5-6-7-8-9-10.
Don't come out. okay?
Meditate here.
Hey. Carlos!
Shit.
Carlos. please don't shoot.
I'm putting my gun down.
I'm putting it down. Don't shoot.
Carlos. I understand your problem.
It's our bloody job.
We don't go home
for three days straight.
Neither does crime end.
nor our duty.
Christmas. New Year come and go
and we don't realise it.
After a shit day.
where do we seek peace of mind?
Our home.
-To a bickering wife.
-(Carlos sobs)
It's a mind fuck.
Hell. don't women know a cop's life
before getting married to them?
How demanding it is!
And why do we work so hard?
For our family.
Correct?
And if the wife has an affair...
Carlos. let it go.
Hey!
Carlos. don't!
(gunfire)
Carlos?
Carlos. tell me...
How will you explain
killing your wife to your son?
For him. every New Year will mean
his father murdering his mother.
A father is a superhero
for his child.
Like Batman
who makes everything okay
at the end.
Forgive your son's mother.
I guarantee your son
will become your fan.
(Carlos sobbing)
(sombre music)
You be with him.
I'll be with my son.
Happy New Year.
(Pedro sighs and exhales)
(sombre music continues)
Sir. how do you do it?
Don't you get scared?
Sir. I've become your fan.
Tonight is embedded
into my core memory.
We must celebrate this.
Sir. let's get drunk!
Sure.
What's your problem?
Why do you drink so much?
Alcohol won't make
your problems vanish.
And milk will?
Maybe not.
But so much alcohol
will make you vanish.
Then. who will care of your grandpa?
Bottoms up!
-Cheers!
-(glasses clink)
Happy New Year. ma'am.
Is this "early"?
I was here at 7 p.m.. Stacey.
I had to go back.
It was a double-murder case.
Tell her. Pritam.
Yes. ma'am. I saw...
a bullet being fired for
the first time in my life. Pedro sir--
Are you the only cop in Goa?
The rest are busy selling feni.
-Stacey. understand--
-How can I?
It was a double-murder case!
Should I have ignored it
to take you for ice cream?
Screw ice cream.
I wanted to cut a cake.
Don't you remember
your son's birthday?
Just today. Pedro.
You can't be on time for one day?
We could've cut cake.
Sung "Happy Birthday."
Leo. let's celebrate your birthday.
Leo. come out.
Where are you. Leo?
Leo!
Where are you? Come out.
(singing)
♪ Happy birthday to you... ♪
♪ Happy... ♪
Pritam. sing!
♪ Happy birthday. dear Leo ♪
Know why Leo isn't coming out?
Do you know?
Because he's dead!
Whether you sing or not.
cut a cake or not.
Leo isn't coming back.
Erase this tattoo
and move on in your life!
I know Leo isn't coming back.
He's never coming back!
But you could've come.
In all of Goa. I need you the most
on this day.
But you're Batman...
saving all of Goa.
So what if your son died.
Leo died because of you!
Stacey. you're crossing the line.
Weren't you supposed to
teach him swimming?
He was waiting for you.
You never came... as always!
So. he jumped into a well.
He didn't jump. He fell.
You were at home?
Why didn't you watch him?
-Should I leave work and babysit?
-Always your work!
I could've been working. too.
I was a singer.
I had offers in Mumbai.
-I sacrificed my career for you.
-Bullshit sacrifice!
You were a bad singer.
Your career never took off.
Don't dump the guilt
of your failure on me.
Don't!
Say sorry.
Why?
I wasn't a bad singer.
Apologise.
I won't.
(sombre music)
Apologise. Or I'll leave you.
Your choice.
(typing)
(phone line ringing)
(soft dramatic music)
It reaches places your hands cannot.
(phone ringing)
Yes. Pedro sir.
Weren't we taught in school -
first A. then B. C. D?
Then why does a keyboard start
with Q?
Does one work
or relearn the alphabet?
Which idiot made this keyboard?
Whichever idiot created it
did a fabulous job.
Sorry.
I'll explain it to you tomorrow.
Bye for now.
Sir. often used letters
are kept separate
or fingers would bump.
But how to remember
where the letters are?
It comes with practice.
If you want.
I can reassign your keys.
To hell with your keys.
Reassign me back
to the Crime Branch.
-or shut up!
-(Pritam chuckles)
I'm a field guy.
I enjoy the fragrance
of bloody crimes.
Like violent assault. chase. murder.
The fragrance of bloody crimes...
wow!
Your fantasies are unlike any other!
Sir. did ma'am return home?
Sir. apologise and end the fight.
I called her.
She didn't answer.
She's throwing attitude.
She's at her parent's house.
Get her back.
I'm not going there.
Sir. why make this an ego issue?
I won't go to bring her back.
nor will I apologise.
I have one goal in life...
going back to the Crime Branch.
I am focussed there.
I know someone who can help you.
Who?
(church bell tolling)
Make a request. Who knows...
(phone ringing)
Yes. Jayant?
Wow!
God answered your prayer.
Ma'am is back home?
We found Grandpa's tape recorder!
Let's go!
I searched everywhere. sir.
Junk dealer. antique shop.
even the Thieves' Market.
This is the one. sir!
Very good.
-Thank you.
-Don't get too touchy.
-You're Superman. Thank you!
-Relax.
I found it
and sir gets the accolades.
There's no cassette. sir.
So? Get a new one.
The cassette had Grandma's voice.
That's the main thing.
What will I do with this?
He found it. Ask him.
Where's the tape?
Lazy bugger!
Sir. I got the body.
What can I do
if someone stole the kidney?
I don't care. I want the kidney.
Find it and put it back!
Impossible!
Finding one cassette in all of Goa.
I haven't gone home in a week.
If I don't.
even my wife will leave...
(TV news reporter) Breaking News.
Goa's Sports Minister DN Sardesai's
8-year-old son has gone missing.
These are the images straight
from the minister's home.
The Deputy Inspector General
has reached the minister's home.
Vinny Sardesai.
the minister's 8-year-old. is missing.
Are you thinking what I am thinking?
Yes. sir.
What?
Didn't he throw you in Cyber hell?
What happens if you find his son?
He'll do as I say.
He'll become your top fan.
He'll transfer me.
-Back to Crime Branch.
-I love it.
The Cyber team must report
to the minister's residence.
DIG's orders.
Sir!
It's said the minister's house
is haunted.
First. things go missing.
Now. the son.
(dramatic music)
Who's got a problem with us?
Are you sure
there's no other angle to this?
I... Let's hope not.
Here's him returning from school.
But no footage of him leaving home.
There's a ghost in this house!
Stuff's gone missing for many days.
First. his grandma's oxygen cylinder.
Then. her bedpan.
I put boiled noodles in the fridge.
They disappeared by morning.
-(phone ringing)
-Hello.
Sir. it's the kidnapper.
Put it on speaker.
Hello?
(man) Good morning. sir.
Oops. sorry...
Your morning
must not be so good. no?
Who is speaking?
Who is speaking is not important.
Listen to what I'm saying.
I'm listening.
For your Vinny...
uh. I want only ₹50 million.
What if...
I don't pay?
Then I'll send you a souvenir
by post.
Your Vinny...
packed in a parcel.
I'll call tomorrow.
You'll need time
to arrange cash. right? (chuckles)
Good day!
Call the Cyber team.
Who's here from Cyber?
Cyber?
Yes. Cyber...
Come.
Sir...
What's he doing here?
Arvind. he's the same fellow...
Don't worry about him.
He's a good officer.
He'll handle it.
-Pedro. trace the call.
-Yes.
Sherlyn... number?
(clears throat)
Run it on TrustCaller.
Yes. sir.
What's the name?
Bobby Sequeira.
-Search social media.
-Yes.
We'll find him. sir.
It's simple.
We'll get him.
How many?
Seven Bobby Sequeiras.
Seven...
How many in Goa?
Just one.
One. sir.
That's our man. Bobby Sequeira.
Owns a bike rental shop.
Stays in Morjim.
We got him. sir. It's that easy.
Get me Bobby Sequeira. Quick!
Morjim.
(police siren blaring)
(doors shut)
(funeral music playing)
Bobby Sequeira? Does he stay here?
Not he. "she." Used to.
"Used to"?
Did she move from here?
Yes.
Where to?
Into the coffin.
When did she die?
Last year. We forgot then.
We're burying her now.
Stop it. What rubbish. Jolly!
Stupid questions get stupid answers.
Did she call anyone before dying?
She was in a coma for two months.
How could she call?
What was her ailment?
Son. she was 102 years.
Old hag wasn't dying.
We had to shoot her.
Let's go.
Crazy old man.
-(phone ringing)
-It's Jayant.
Yes. Jayant?
Bobby Sequeira
was a 102-year-old woman.
She'd rent out her ID card.
Cyber fraudsters bought SIM cards
using it.
What next? Get the body?
Shut up. Jayant!
You should've traced
the SIM's location. not its owner.
It's common bloody sense.
This guy's a fraud.
He'll bring any child
and say it's my Vinny.
Get him off the case.
Do you understand?
Get out of here!
Sir...
Do you not know how to follow orders?
I said get out! Now!
I want to say something
before I leave.
Police know how to do their job.
Ministers like you don't let us.
Your ego gets hurt.
Like when I said.
your wife's phone was in the house.
A two-minute chat with Vinny...
I was doing my job.
With full honesty.
Two minutes then.
and Vinny would be here today.
Pedro. stop it.
Stop. sir?
You moved me from Crime Branch
and made me the head of Cyber.
I don't even get
why a keyboard starts with Q!
Finding letters is a pain.
How do I trace a phone number?
I don't get cybercrime.
Let me solve cases my way.
I promise I'll find Vinny.
You didn't let me do my job then.
nor now.
Pedro. you'll be suspended.
Suspend me. sir.
I'm wasted here anyway.
I'll while away time at home.
No one knows the loss of a son
better than me.
I'll give you
a cyber genius' number.
He located a stolen ATM
in 15 minutes.
Talk to him respectfully.
If he's in the mood. he might help you.
Good luck with the case.
(dramatic music)
Let me through.
Sir!
I'll update--
I'll tell you everything.
Please wait!
(taps on window)
Minister sir has apologised.
He's said to stay on the case
along with your cyber genius.
The kidnapper will call
tomorrow at 9 a.m.
(dramatic music)
(theme song)
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm